- What beverage do you make for that?
- Oh, no, no, no, I know this.
(Leonard:)- Hot apple cider with cinnamon sticks?
- Hot apple cider with cinnamon sticks.
What the frig, Cooper?
We were supposed to be in my office
half an hour ago.
(Sheldon:)And yet now you're in my office.
Point Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Welcome to the thunderdome, Kripke.
We agreed to exchange copies of our work.
Let me see yours.
Why don't you show me yours first?
You think I just fell off the turnip truck?
(Kripke:)We exchange at the same time.
(Sheldon:)How do I know you're not going
to take my ideas and publish them?
How do I know you're not gonna?
Yeah, because I'm not interested
in getting published in MAD Magazine.
The zingers fly fast
in the thunderdome, Barry.
Are we gonna do this or not?